<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Craig Sullivan&#39;s Github Site</title>
    <link>/categories/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Craig Sullivan&#39;s Github Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How My Machine Learning Bracket Did</title>
      <link>/2021/04/09/how-my-machine-learning-bracket-did/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/04/09/how-my-machine-learning-bracket-did/</guid>
      <description>In our bracket group I finished 8th and in the 79.6 percentile of all brackets. In our class that was almost squarely in the middle of the pack though I did finish one spot above “I Miss Teddy Allen”. Our brackets seemed to be closely correlated because at the start of the challenge we were only separated by one spot at the bottom of the class. Overall, I think my model did a fine job of picking brackets as evidenced by being almost in the 80th percentile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How My Machine Learning Predicted My Whole Bracket</title>
      <link>/2021/03/23/how-my-machine-learning-predicted-my-whole-bracket/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/03/23/how-my-machine-learning-predicted-my-whole-bracket/</guid>
      <description>Coming into the year I had watched a lot of college basketball, sometimes multiple games per day. As my own college and classwork stepped up so did my free time to watch as much basketball. I still watched every Nebraska game start to finish and various other top 25 programs but I never saw Oral Roberts or Loyola Chicago this year.
To supplement my lack of first hand experience with some of the field of 64 this year I made a model that predicted the outcome of each game with a win or loss prediction.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
